多谢惠顾
Thank you.
那是我们今晚的第十位同志顾客了
That was, like, our tenth gay guy tonight.
希望这股同志人气比骚当的还要持久
Let's hope our gay buzz lasts longer than Adam Lambert's
噢 会的 我都投身下去
Oh, it will. I'm all over it.
我指的是我都投身在grindr了
And by "It," I mean I'm all over grindr.
Max 你为什么用那App
Max, why are you on that app?
你又不是要约炮的同志
You're not a gay man looking for anonymous sex.
别给姐定型
Don't put me in a box!
你告诉我要找法子招揽生意
You told me to find ways to drum up business.
而我在用这家伙的巨J来招揽
Well, I'm drumming it up by showing off this guy's "Bid'ness."
我装作一个粗犷
I pretended to be a rough and
想着得到抱抱的波多黎各同志
ready Puerto Rican guy who still likes to cuddle.
同志密友就是如此好用
That there's gay chum, my friend.
噢 我又勾引了个猛男了 拿网来
Ooh, I hooked a big one. Get the net.
嗨 刚有个波多黎各猛男在此吗
Hi. Was a muscular Puerto Rican guy just here?
他不是刚在这吗
When is there not?
你想在等的时候买个杯子蛋糕吗
Would you like to purchase a delicious cupcake while you wait?
好吧 反正我等着
Well, maybe, while I wait.
我的电话说他在此
My phone says he's right here.
来 我们请客
Here, this is on the house,
因为他就是那猛男
because the muscular gay guy, that's him.
你是在变性没关系
It's cool that you're transitioning,
但你应该坦白自己不是波多黎各人
but you really should let people know you're not Puerto Rican.
他说自己是22岁 充满男人味 我也很不满好吗
Well.... He said he was 22 and butch, so I'm mad too.
== 破产姐妹 第三季 第8集 ==
【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献
== 翻译:大姨妈 蜜蜜 尧之雪 特特 天之行者 ==
== 校对&时间轴:天之行者  统筹:尧之雪  后期:忘枫 ==
本字幕仅用于交流 学习之用
禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
Earl 我要今晚的结帐单
Earl, I need my checks for tonight.
- 美丽动人  - 确定
- Beautiful? - Check.
- 性感诱人  - 确定
- Sexy? - Check.
- 酷炫狂拽吊炸天  - 确定
- Cool? - Check.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
我早来10分钟接班
I was ten minutes early for my shift,
所以我想有20分钟可以消磨
so I thought "Well, I have 20 minutes to kill,"
而我闲逛到一间很酷的冲浪用品店
and I wandered into this cool surf shop
我见到一个汉纸在给冲浪板抛光
and saw this guy polishing a surfboard.
一个在此的冲浪者
A surfer here?
你不会在威廉斯堡冲浪的 这儿只是上吊胜地
You don't hang ten in Williamsburg, you hang yourself.
我认同Max说的
I'm with Max, the only waves
布鲁克林区有的只是热浪 以及罪恶浪潮
we get in Brooklyn are heat waves and crime waves.
- Earl 你从没去沙滩的吗  - 妹纸你疯了吗
- Earl, you never go out to the beach? - You crazy?
我才不去当鲨鱼粮食
I'm ain't gonna get eaten by some shark.
而且也没这种时间
Ain't nobody got time for that.
你会鲨鱼咬的机率也就0.0001%而已
The chances of you being bit by a shark are, like, .0001%.
黑人例外
Not if you're black.
鲨鱼种族歧视妥妥的
Sharks are racist as hell.
这是它们叫"大白鲨"的缘故
That's why they call them "Great whites."
那冲浪者 Marc 我跟他很合缘
Marc, the surfer, and I really hit it off,
他很可爱
and he is so cute, like a
而且他像年轻版 一头真发的Matthew McConaughey
young Matthew McConaughey, but with real hair.
那即是没半点像Matthew McConaughey
So nothing like Matthew McConaughey.
真希望他给我短讯 我爱死冲浪了
I hope he texts me. I love surfing.
我从不下水
I never go in the water,
因为我晓得一但下沉 我会随着去的
'cause I know if I start drowning, I'm not gonna fight it.
我过去在夏天
When I used to summer in
待在St. Barths时 有几个意大利冲浪猛男
St.Barths, there'd be these sexy Italian surfers,
他们还邀请我们在冲浪上做日光浴
and they'd invite us to sunbathe on their boards.
虽然他们是抢劫了我们 但那经历太美好了
I mean, they robbed us, but it was amazing.
Caroline 要是你在找爱水男儿
Caroline, if you're looking for that kind of guy,
我有个表弟很爱待在海
I have a cousin who loves the water.
因为那是他唯一能动脚的地方
It's the only place he can move his legs.
- 噢 拍谢不用了  - 考虑一下
- Oh, sweet. No thanks. - Well, think about it.
你可以在任一演唱会坐前排
You'll be at the front row of every concert,
而且他还不会翻睡
and he doesn't move around a lot when he sleeps.
来 把我号码给辆椅男
Here, give old Ironside my number.
啥了 我热爱音乐 而且要是他对我抓狂
What? I love music, and if he bugs me,
随时能找辆警车来抓他回家
the city has one of those free vans that'll take him home.
冲浪男约我晚餐了
It's the surfer asking me out to dinner!
而且他想能带我去
And he thinks he can get us into the hot,
新潮热点"Harlow and Daughters"
new spot, Harlow and Daughters.
噢 就是那取代了完美的"hot dog on a stick"
Oh, that's that trendy restaurant that replaced
的主题餐厅吧
a perfectly good hot dog on a stick.
晚安了 穷逼两后
Good night, broke-ass divas.
晚安 断背侍应
Good night, Brokeback waiter.
我要去做按摩
I'm gonna go get a massage,
然后呢 或者要来一发吧
and then, who knows? Maybe give one.
噢 我在说啥 明天我来时肯定有了
Oh, who am I kidding? I'm coming back here pregnant.
- Luis 明天你能帮我顶班吗  - 当然~不~行
- Luis, can you work for me tomorrow? - Absolutely not, no.
Oleg明天上班 我会叫他穿鱼网背心上衣
Oleg's working, and I'll ask him to wear his fishnet tank top.
那好
Then yes.
跟个可爱男生晚餐 而且还能在热门餐厅里
Dinner with a cute guy who has connections to the "A"-list place?
我重获旧生了
I'm living my old life.
嘿 各位
Hey, everybody.
你的昔日包括这吗
Did your old life have one of these?
Caroline 我是餐厅首要规矩是什么
Caroline, what is my number-one diner rule?
千万别跟人家说肉是假的
Don't tell anyone the meat isn't real?
嘘 少来 肉见故肉真
Shh. Come on. If you can see it, it's real.
别跟人家说你在朋友后车厢买的虾子
Don't tell anyone you buy the shrimp out of your friend's trunk?
他有用毛毯包着好吗 不是这回事
He lays down a blanket! No.
不能用电话
No phones.
Max 他订到位子了
Max, he got us the reservation!
我要去新热点餐厅吃晚饭了
I'm going to dinner at the new "It" Place.
噢 新热点
Ooh, the "It" Place!
"来去新热点吃晚餐吧"
"Let's have dinner at the 'it' place."
为何这儿不是热点
How come this isn't the "It" Place?
这非但不是热点 更像是黑点吧
This isn't an "It" Place. It's more of an "It" Hole.
好吧 那我们要如何才能令此成为热点
Okay, so how do we become an "It" Place?
首先 一把火烧光这儿 重新装潢
First, burn the place down, start fresh.
然后你再制造出
Then you create hype by
一股难以预订的热潮
making it impossible to get a reservation.
基本上就是把所有人都拒绝了
You basically refuse to let anyone in.
我可以第一个拒绝吗
Can I be the first?
好了 我把约会包带上啦
Okay, I've put my date purse together.
口香糖 眼镜齐全
I've got my gum, my gloss,
这20刀让我看起来有钱
and a $20 bill to make it seem like I have money,
我明天会把这钱还回餐厅收银机去的
which I will return to the register at the diner tomorrow.
欢迎你用我的约会包
Well, you're welcome to use my date purse.
有装着雪茄和四角裤的保鲜袋
It's a Ziploc with a cigar and a change of boxers.
手机电充满了
And my phone is fully charged,
可以用高档叫车服务来载我回家
so I can call an uber car to take me home.
高档叫车
An uber car?
你才坐不起高级轿车
You can't afford a fancy town car.
就在昨天 你还拿英式松饼做去角质呢
Yesterday, you used an English muffin to exfoliate.
是啊 然后我还把它吃了呢
Yeah, and then I ate it.
再说了 这信用卡我们俩联名的
Plus, it's on our joint credit card,
意味着你傻逼下用了钱
which means every time you make a dumb purchase,
你也欠我的
you owe me a joint.
我不想让他送我回家
I don't want to have him
然后再误会什么
take me home and give him the wrong idea.
别这样 请让他误会什么吧
Oh, please do give him the wrong idea.
整晚都跟那个冲浪男一起吧
Stay out all night with the surfer.
在单板U型场浪一下
Ride his half-pipe.
这不是冲浪板  是滑雪板
That's not surfboard, that's snowboard.
完美啊 因为我对这个对话感到厌烦了
Perfect, 'cause I'm snow-bored with this conversation.
如何 这对咪咪效果好吗
What do you think? These things on full display?
我不想成为那种讨人厌的室友
I hate to be that roommate,
但我没说你可以把借我的咪咪
but I didn't say you could borrow my breasts.
什么 这就是个集中型胸罩
What? It's just a push-up bra,
外加胸垫 一些纸巾 以及胶贴
chicken cutlets, a little tissue, and some tape.
多纯天然
You know, natural.
快去约会吧
Just go on your date already!
Nancy和我一直在盼着你走
Nancy and I have been really looking forward to you leaving
这样我们可以光着身子走 顺便来玩猫薄荷
so we can walk around naked and do some lines of cat nip.
哦 这个肯定是他 别担心 他不会进来的
Ooh, that must be him. Don't worry, he's not coming inside.
最好不 我们养不起孩子
He better not, cause we can't afford a baby.
- 噢 就是Sophie  -  就是Sophie
- Oh, it's just Sophie. - "Just Sophie"?
这个我在波兰的脱口秀节目名字啊
That was the name of my talk show in Poland.
我多希望我能上那个节目啊
Oh, how I wish I could have been a guest on that show.
不 没有嘉宾 就是只有Sophie
No, there were no guests. It was just Sophie!
Caroline 你准备好去约会了啊
Oh, you getting ready for your big date, Caroline?
你怎么知道我有约会
How did you hear about my date?
很简单 你的声音
Oh, well, your voice travels.
我承认 我听到那些有的没得
Yeah, I hear everything that does and doesn't happen
这儿或那儿的声音
down here and down there, so...
我只是很开心你要去约会了
So let's just say I'm very glad that you're going on a date.
对了 我给你带了点小礼物
Oh, and I got you a little present.
肉桂味的薄荷糖 你的初吻
Cinnamon mints, for your first kiss.
哦 真贴心 Sophie
Oh, that's so sweet, Sophie.
是啊 我还给你带了一大袋的套子
Yeah, and I got you a big grab bag of condoms.
尺寸齐全
I got all sizes.
大号 超大号
I got magnums, I got super magnums,
普通 还有
I got regular, and...
他是个好人
"He's got a great personality."
给你
Here you go.
通常情况下 "好人"就是我唯一的不碰的
Usually, a "Great personality" Is the only birth control I need.
谢谢你 但是我是个淑女
Thank you, but I am a lady,
不到第三次约会 我还不想用这个
and I won't be needing these until our third date.
你可得快点打扮好
Well, you better hurry up and get dressed.
Sophie 我已经打扮好了
Sophie, I'm already dressed.
你~确定
You are?
我喜欢今天的这身
And I like what I'm wearing.
真的~吗
You do?
那脸上画点小妆
Well, just put on a little makeup.
我已经画好妆了
I'm fully made up.
你~确定
You are?
或许你可以弄一下你的发型
Oh, well, you know, maybe when you do your hair.
我是有点没把发型放心上
Okay, I'm a little behind on my hair.
我把胸部看作头等大事了
My boobs were a bigger project than I thought.
我喜欢我这身打扮 也没时间去换了
And I like what I'm wearing, and I don't have time to change
因为他已经迟到二十分钟了
'cause he's already 20 minutes late.
迟到二十分钟
20 minutes late?
哇
Wahh-wahh.
这就意味着他不来了
That's a no-show.
你被放鸽子了 那人凶残地放你鸽子了
You've just got stood up. You got stood up somethin' awful.
我才没被放鸽子 我从来没被放过鸽子
I did not get stood up. I've never been stood up.
事实上  我都不知道我是不是被放鸽子了
In fact, I wouldn't even know if I was being stood up,
因为我好像没什么机会被放鸽子
because that's how little I know about being stood up.
我被放鸽子了吗
Am I being stood up?
才没有 男人都是爱迟到的
No, you are not. Guys are always late.
由此我等一个男的等了三天
I once waited three days for a guy.
他终于带着赎金出现了
But he showed up with the ransom money,
然后我再也不用待在冰箱里面了
and you don't see me living in a fridge anymore.
好吧
Okay, fine.
没人被放鸽子
Nobody got stood up.
我就坐在这儿 发短信等着
So I'll just sit here and text while we wait...
大概 永远吧
You know, forever.
当破晓来临的时候
And then, finally, when it dawns on you,
我们呼唤我们的老朋友 Oleg 抓他出气
we can call our friend Oleg, and he can go put a hit on him.
也许 他觉得我们定在约会的地点见面
You know what, maybe he thought we were meeting there.
我打电话给餐厅看看
I'm calling the restaurant to see...
对 你好 Marc Faison有来吗
Yes, hi, has a Marc Faison checked in yet?
还没
He has not.
现在呢
What about now?
也许他
It's just that he was supposed...
我也很忙啊
Well, I'm busy too.
别这么狂 你那先前还不是"hot dog on a stic"
Don't be so snooty, you used to be a hot dog on a stick.
顺便说一声 如果他还不出现 那我就还是要裸着
Just a heads up, if he doesn't show, I'm still getting naked.
哦 他来了啊
Ooh, there he is!
不 是亚马逊的
No, it's from Amazon.
有人要送我套"他其实没那么喜欢你"的碟
Someone's sending me a copy of He's Just Not That Into You.
哈 妹纸 就是我
Yeah, I'm here for you, girl.
好吧 我被放鸽子了
Well, I got stood up.
Max 记住这一刻
Remember where you are, Max.
这一天Caroline Channing被放鸽子了
This was the day Caroline Channing got stood up.
去他的什么约会
Well, screw him for standing you up.
从现在开始 绝不要相信一个不找黄片的男人
And from now on, never trust a guy who surfs anything besides porn.
喔 看那 "Harlow and Daughters"
Oh, look, Harlow and Daughters
有种旧时杂货店的感觉
has a real old-timey, general store kind of vibe.
我想他们可能是把"星期四回顾"太当真了
I guess they take "Throwback Thursday" Really seriously here.
我是说 这可是1840年啊
I mean, it's 1840.
是啊 我也想带你回到你没被放鸽子前的时候
Yeah, I wanted to take you back to a time before you were stood up.
Max 感谢你带我来这里
Thank you for making me take the reservation, Max.
我是说 否则我只能爬到床上然后独自哭泣到天明了
I mean, otherwise, I was just gonna get in bed and be depressed.
你刚才不就这么干呢吗
You were in bed and you were depressed.
别因为这帮人在重写历史 你也这么干
Don't rewrite history just 'cause these folks have.
我们人在威廉斯堡讽刺风格里
I mean, we are smack in the belly
我得要滋味一下
of Williamsburg ironic chic, and I want to smack it.
看 他们甚至还有挂着小孩衣服的乡村风晒衣绳
Look, they even have a country clothesline hung with baby clothes..
我们真该给Han带回去
We should get this for Han.
这真是我见过最做作的一件东西
I mean, that is the most pretentious thing I've ever seen.
你们好 欢迎来到Harlow and Daughters 我是这儿的老板 我叫Brain-Brain
Hi, welcome to Harlow and Daughters. I'm the host, Brian-Brian.
我刚才错了 他才是
No, that is.
哈喽 呃 Brian-Brian
Yes, hi, um, Brian-Brian.
我们有预订 名字是Faison 两个人
We have a reservation. Faison, party of two.
你们俩都到齐了吗
Is your whole party here?
这个嘛 我不知道还能怎么到齐
Well, I don't know how whole
因为我是个私生子
I could ever hope to be, as I'm illegitimate.
是的 我们都到了 多谢你
Yes, we're both here. Thank you.
所以你和Faison先生都在这里
So both you and Mr. Faison are here?
是啊 大家都知道我变性了
Yes, I'm transitioning. Ask around.
你们可以先拿杯喝的 当有空位的时候我会叫你们
You can have a drink, and I'll call you when your table is ready.
多谢你 多谢你 Brian-Brian
Thank you, thank you, Brian-Brian.
我就在这儿呆着了
I'll be right over.
赶紧用你的大胸给我们在吧台找个地儿坐
Go use your new boobs to get us a seat at the bar.
你好 我知道什么叫 在吧台等候
Hi, I know what "Wait by the bar" Means.
从你这套衣服流行之后 我就一直在餐厅工作了
I've been working in restaurants since your clothes were in style.
它意味着我会给你们找地方坐 当你们的
It means I'll seat you when your...
Brian-Brian 阿B 阿B 小B 小B 别来这套
Brian-Brian, Bri-Bri, B.B., come on.
咱俩都清楚根本就没有其他男人要来
You and I both know there's no guy coming.
我朋友被放鸽子了 所以你就别把事情弄得更糟了
My friend got stood up, so please don't make things worse.
赶紧把你的酷酷的
Just take out your cool,
小猎刀拿出来 放我们一马
little hunting knife and cut us some slack.
我会给你现金小费 或者让你上了我
This is where I'd tip you with cash or offer you sex,
但是我破产了 而你看着也像个基佬 所以你还是友好点吧
but I'm kinda broke and you're kinda gay, so just be nice.
我们一般不把性向跟工作搅在一起
We don't really need to bring my sexuality into it.
我懂 就像100年前一样困难
I understand, it's hard to be out 100 years ago.
真有趣
Oh, funny.
这边走 Faison先生
Right this way, Mr. Faison.
哇 ，那真快 他们在这里真好
Wow, that was quick. They're so nice here.
是的 只是普通的人 坐在设计师的泡菜桶里
Yep, just regular folks, sitting around designer pickle barrels.
好吧 这里是你的座位 请坐
All right, here's your table. Have a seat.
好吧 哪里 在这我们都叫做椅子
Sure, where? On these Amish
的阿米什人分娩椅上面吗
birthing stools we're all calling chairs?
开同性恋的玩笑就够了
Stick to the gay jokes.
我们的WIFI密码在牛皮上
Our Wi-Fi password is on the ox hide.
你的服务员马上过来
Your waitress will be right over.
Max 服务员马上会过来啊 而那不会是我们
Max, a waitress will be right over, and it won't be us.
看 满是肮脏木屑的地板
Look, dirty sawdust floors.
如果我们有一袋木屑
If we got a bag of wood chips,
我们的公寓会是新的热点
our apartment could be the new "It" Place.
你好 我叫York
Hello, my name is York.
难以置信 一个男的叫Brian-Brian也能被完爆
Hard to believe, but a man named Brian-Brian has been dethroned.
York吗 真好玩 约是纽约的纽吗
York? That's fun. "York" As in "New"?
"约"就是"约" 只是York
York as in York. Just York.
那你是哪家"女表"
So what's this bit?
好吧 York 我们想点喝的
Okay. Well, um, York, we'd like to start with some drinks.
女孩之夜开始了 所以单身女孩举起手来
Having a girls' night out. All the single ladies put ya hands up!
这迫不得的
Yeah, you can't force it.
我们今晚特别的酒是“天花”
Our special libation this evening is "The Small Pox."
这是苦艾酒 丁香和橘子苦酒
It's absinthe, cloves, orange bitters
在玻璃瓶手摇的
hand-muddled in a mason jar.
这个喝的是Wes Anderson发明的吗
Was that drink directed by Wes Anderson?
我们只是要尽快
Can we just get two of your
的来两杯最便宜的"Ye olde"啤酒
"Ye olde" Cheapest beers as soon as possible?
因为Quinn博士 我需要一些药 女人
Because Dr. Quinn, I need some medicine, woman.
York 特别汤里面有大蒜吗
York, does the special soup have any garlic?
- 哦 天哪 不可能  - 什么 有人制造肥皂吗
- Oh, my God, no way! - What? Is someone making soap?
没有 没有大蒜吗
No. No garlic?
你还一直觉得那冲浪男会来
You still think the surfer's coming.
是的 他可能来
Well, he might.
看 我理应和那男人约会
See, I was supposed to have a date with this guy...
你不在乎的 所以 喝汤吗
You don't care. So, the soup?
当然 我现在只是想要饮料单
Actually, I'm just taking drink orders right now.
哇 谁爱你
Wow, who loved you?
额 我猜她从来没和她妈妈的大麻贩子
Eh, I'm guessing she never went
一起去父女舞会
to a father/daughter dance with her mom's weed dealer.
你不懂 Max 可能他丢了手机
You don't know, Max. Maybe he lost his phone
或者他没有我的号码 所以他只好回到这里
and he didn't have my number, so he's on his way running here.
你觉得他会湿漉漉的出现
You think he's just gonna rush in soaking wet
就像说:哦 不好意思 交通太差了
and be like, "Oh, I'm so sorry. The traffic was terrible.
车都排成龙了
The waves were bumper-to-bumper."
这不是一部Katherine Heigl的电影
This is not a Katherine Heigl movie.
不好意思 电影哦
Sorry, "Movie."
好了 他不来了
Fine, he's not coming.
我才不稀罕Katie Heigl的什么烂电影呢
And I'm not getting into the Katie Heigl thing.
至少此时此地是这样 还是尝尝这橡子吧
Not here, not now. Let's just enjoy our acorns.
哦 "未知号码" 说不定是他打来的呢 喂
Ooh, "Blocked number." Maybe it's him. Hello?
傻妞儿 挂了吧 他连个鬼影都不会有的
Hang up. He's not coming.
我们喝的东西就在那儿
Our drinks are right there.
它们正在那边等着我们呢 就在吧台上
I can see them over yonder, on ye olde bar.
都一个小时了 我们那个女招待 Lizzie Borden 哪儿去了
It's been an hour, where is our waitress, Lizzie Borden?
或许正在后台琢磨还有什么发音能更怪些的词呢
Probably in the back deciding which words to pronounce weirdly.
饿死老娘了 给姐扯块儿胸垫
I'm starving. Bust out those chicken cutlets.
怪不得他们没有收到任何yelp的差评呢
No wonder they don't have any bad yelp reviews.
压根儿就没人给上菜
No one's ever tasted their food.
嗨 我们点的饮料呢
Hi. Um, our drinks?
问过大厨汤的事情了吗
And did you ask the chef about the soup?
不好意思 我还没腾出空来
You know, I haven't had a minute.
她还没腾出空来
She hasn't had a minute?
那她都干啥啦 演"与狼共舞"啦
What's she been doing, dancing with wolves?
我说 你遇到过这情况吗
I mean, have you ever?
就是 你还能忍吗
I know, can you even?
我和Byron都等半天了
Byron and I have been here forever,
我们的蒲公英鹰嘴豆鹅肝到现在还没上
and have yet to see our dandelion chickpea foie-gras.
他低血糖 我是Lila
He's hypoglycemic and I'm Lila.
我是怒了 我去搞定喝的
And I'm pissed. I'm getting our drinks.
- 能麻烦你给我们也来点儿吗  - 没问题 想喝什么
- Would you get us some wine? - Oh, sure, what kind?
给我来点儿霞多丽 Byron白索维农就行
A chardonnay for me, and Byron will have a sauvignon blanc.
- Max 你这是要干嘛 他们会把我们赶出去的 还有  - 还有啥 又怎么了 Caroline
- Max, no, they'll kick us out and... - And what? What, Caroline?
难道担心"他来的时候" 你已经不在了
You won't be here when "He arrives?"
姑奶奶啊 那个人不会来的
Dear Lord, the man is not coming!
我知道 Max 他肯定来不了啦 因为他死了
I know that, Max, and he's not coming because he died.
他死了 这样说我才能好受些
He died, that's the only reason I can accept.
怎么样啊 今晚过得如何
What's up? How we all doin' tonight?
糟糕透了 我女朋友刚把我踹了
Not so good. My girlfriend just broke up with me.
哦 是嘛 那你喜欢金发妞嘛
Oh, yeah? You like blondes?
我身边就有一个 随约随走
'Cause I got one who's ready to pop.
还是算了吧 我喜欢亚洲妞儿
No, man, I'm into Asian chicks.
有谁不喜欢呢 不过亚洲男人例外吧
Yeah, who isn't? Except for Asian guys.
嘿 能帮个忙嘛 多待数分钟
Hey, do me a favor, just wait a minute,
到我那桌 逗逗我朋友
and then come over to my table and flirt with my friend.
有什么好处
Why would I do that?
这个我请
On the house.
这是那个"蒲公英鹰嘴豆
Is that the "Dandelion chickpea and other things
还有一堆不靠谱"的菜吗
that don't belong in a dish together" Thing?
搞定了 你的蒲公英鹰嘴豆
All right, your dandelion chickpea,
一杯霞多丽 还有白索维农 慢慢享用
a chardonnay, and a sauvignon blanc. Enjoy.
你们在干嘛呢
What do you think you're doing?
当然是招待客人了啊 好好学着点儿
Waiting on tables. Look into it.
York York 千万别生气 Byron和我们都饥渴难耐
York, York, don't be mad. Byron was starving and we're thirsty.
千万别赶我们走 我们连爬的力气都没有了
Don't kick us out, we're too weak to go anywhere else.
汤里有大蒜
The soup has garlic.
哦 那就不要了 来份儿马哈鱼吧
Oh, then no. The salmon, please.
给她上那个汤 今晚没人要和她亲嘴
Bring her the damn soup, she ain't kissing nobody tonight.
给我来份儿以为能虎口逃生的
And I'll have the free-range
走地鸡肉
chicken that thought it had a chance.
谢谢你的帮助 Byron希望你能收下这个
For your help. Byron wants you to have it.
Byron才是这里最懂规矩的人
Well, Byron is the only real old-fashioned thing in here.
祝你们长命百岁
I hope you both survive the winter.
嘿 介意我坐这儿吗
Hey, can I join you?
哦 我想这句话是对你说的哦
Ooh, I think that "Can I join you?" Was to you.
当然可以 请坐
Oh, sure, have a seat.
你真漂亮 身材好极了
You're pretty. You have a good body.
喔噢 多谢夸奖
Wow, thank you.
事实上 这话听起来真好
That's actually kind of nice to hear,
虽然难以置信
because this is hard to believe,
但我今晚被放鸽子了
but I got stood up tonight,
所以你夸我漂亮 身材好
and it kind of makes me feel good
我真的很开心
when you say I'm pretty and I have a good body.
你做什么呢
What are you doing?
我在上tinder 就像是正常向的grindr
Oh, I'm on tinder. It's the straight grindr.
有人约我炮 得走了
I just got a hit. Well, I'm out.
谢谢请我喝酒
Thanks for the drink.
你花钱雇人夸我漂亮
You paid a guy to say I'm pretty?
然后他又把我甩了
And then he blew me off?
哦 天呐 我刚想到一件郁闷的事情
Oh, my God. I just realized something upsetting.
是什么 我们马上就能
What, that we could be
到"hot dogs on sticks"吃热狗吗
enjoying delicious hot dogs on sticks right now?
- 不是 我是"B"  - 不 你是A罩杯
- No, I'm a "B." - No, you're an "A."
你今天穿的胸罩托得像B罩杯而已
That bra just makes you look like a "B."
不是 我是说作为女人 我不是最好的
No, I mean me, as a woman. I'm a "B."
要知道 一直以来 我都觉得自己是最好的呢
You know, all this time, I kinda thought I was an "A,"
但也许我只是个"B"等货
but maybe I'm just a "B."
要不为什么刚才那个人甩了我 而那个冲浪的又放我鸽子
That's why he walked away and why the surfer stood me up.
Caroline 我真想在这儿听你唠叨
Caroline, I really want to be here for you right now,
但我要给角落里那个采矿的端杯杜松子酒过去
but I gotta get a gin fizz to the prospector in the corner.
Max 我真的没那么好吗 为什么他都不来呢
Max, am I a "B"? Why didn't he come?
我能告诉你的就是那个冲浪的就是个"D"等货
All I know about that surfer is that he is a "D"
"D"后面还有三个字母呢
followed by three other letters.
我倒真想写出来给你看
I'd spell it out for you,
但我实在不相信自己的那点儿拼写水平
but I'm literally afraid I'd get it wrong.
你竟然也没否定我是"B"等货
Interesting that you didn't say I wasn't a "B."
听着 姐这辈子从来没用字母给自己打过分
Look, I don't give myself letters in life.
对我来说 那就是过及不过的区别
To me, it is clearly a pass/fail situation.
振作点儿
And you're sitting up,
别自恋 神马都是浮云
not drooling on yourself, so pass.
妞儿们这一晚上都去哪儿疯了
Well, well, well, where have you ladies been all night?
我也搞不清 可能穿越到1846年到1860年的某个地方了吧
I don't know, I'd say somewhere between 1846 and 1860.
能回到1974年真是太好了
And it is so great to be back in 1974.
不错嘛 Han 你干得不错啊 让这个店变得更高档了
Well, Han, you did a good job of making this place exclusive.
高档到没人来光顾啊
There is literally nobody here.
这跟我屁点儿关系都没有 都是刚才男厕里那只负鼠搞的鬼
It wasn't my doing, there was a possum in the men's room.
纠正一下 是现在仍在男厕的那只负鼠
Correction, there is a possum in the men's room.
哦 厨房上演食材大逃亡了吗
Oh, the ingredients are escaping the kitchen again?
我要就去厕所揪出那只负鼠
Well, I gotta go to the men's room and pull out the possum.
哦 我俩不在时你就是这么干的吗
Oh, is that what you do when we're not here?
好了 坐下吧
All right, let's sit down
就坐那个破的快散架了的卡座 再来点吃的
in that authentically run-down old booth and eat something.
是啊 看见没 别以为那地方是污迹 那可真的是血迹哦
Yeah, see, those stains aren't fake, that's real blood.
那家伙被捅的时候我可就在现场
I was right here when that guy got stabbed.
就像我上次说的
Like I said at the time,
"再敢叫我亲爱的 信不信我捅你"
"Call me 'honey' one more time, and I will stab you."
猜我怎么想
You know what I just realized?
即使不是最好的 那我至少也货真价实
Even if I am a "B," At least I'm an authentic "B."
我就是我 不会惺惺作态
I don't pretend to be something I'm not.
才怪呢 你就是假装过
You do kind of pretend to be something you're not.
那对假咪咪
A "B."
终于有顾客了
Finally, I have some customers.
要知道 我可是坐在后台
You know, I've been sitting in
看着Oleg在那里撸整晚的
the back watching Oleg shuck his corn all night?
谢大神
Thank you.
现在Luis学会怎么做事了哦
Now, Luis knows how to give service.
算了吧 菇凉 可别这么说 这可是相当的简单
Come on, chica, don't set me up like that, it's too easy.
Max 我觉得还是不要用字母等级来评价自己了
Max, I think I'm gonna let go of letter-grading myself
决定采用你的过及不过理论
and adopt your pass/fail system.
我现在和你面对面而坐就说明我够格了
And sitting with you right here is so not a fail.
哦 是Oleg和Sophie
Oh, it's just Oleg and Sophie.
哦 好家伙 你还肖想
Oh, my God! You looked 'cause you thought
那个冲浪男  烂到渣
it was gonna be the surfer! Epic fail!
嘿 你们两个怎么又在一起了
Hey, what are you two doing together?
哦 Sophie和我干了件大事
Oh, Sophie and I had some business to take care of.
是吧 Sophie
Right, Sophie?
是啊 Caroline 我们挺你哦
Oh, yeah. Caroline, we got your back.
那个Mike要有段时间不敢再出来冲浪了
That Mike won't be out there surfing again for quite a while.
那个冲浪男的名字不叫Mike 他叫Marc
The surfer's name isn't Mike. It's Marc.
哦
Oh...
怪不得他一直在叫唤说 "我不叫Marc"
No wonder he kept screaming, "My name is not Marc!"
好吧 我得跟你说
Well, I'll tell you one thing,
今天晚上我们遇上的假货太多
we may have seen a lot of fake things tonight,
但那可是一只如假包换的负鼠哦
but that's a for-real possum.
哇哦 Han的负鼠可比我想的大多了
Wow, Han's possum is bigger than I thought it would be.
目前总资产：2420刀
== 破产姐妹 第三季 第8集【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献 ==
== 【H-SGDK】字幕组欢迎各位加入
有意者请加QQ群109164858，注明 字幕组+申请职位即可 ==
Adam Lambert 骚当 出柜后人气持续高涨
Grindr 是一个供男同志使用的跨平台社交软体
Checks在餐厅里可指帐单 同时Max也在玩"检定"的双关
Hang Ten既是来自美国加州的休闲服饰
而其口号Hanging Ten---意指双脚紧贴冲浪板
Matthew McConaughey目前发线后移得很……
Ironside "轮椅神探"剧集 本季新版3集即取消
Hot Dog on a Stick 创立于1946年的美国标志性品牌
热狗棒或起司棒是标志食品
去角质 原本是用各种不同大小的去角质颗粒来达致磨砂的效果
这儿C姐应该是用英式松饼磨脸了……
Joint同时解作大麻
Half-pipe亦解妹纸把人家弄得性奋后停下来的意思
Come inside同时解内射
小J梗
他其实没那么喜欢你 2009年电影
Bitch梗
Wes Anderson的电影有强烈的个人风格
Dr. Quinn, Medicine Woman 1993-1998剧集 风格古老
大蒜能制造肥皂
Lizzie Borden 涉嫌把生父和继母乱刀砍死
yelp 美国著名商户点评网站
与狼共舞 1990年相当知名的电影 此片描述美国在1860年代
D~I~C~K Dick~! (混蛋)
估计是说掏J梗……